Conan Mafnas

Manassas, VA 20112 mafnasca@gmail.com (571) 292-6830

Applying for the Web Developer Job / Internship Position

Address 13274 Amblewood Drive, Manassas, VA 20112

Phone (571) 292-6830

E-mail mafnasca@gmail.com

Date of birth 16 Mar 1996

I have been very passionate upon programming since I was 15 years old. I have worked on personal projects using primarily the back-end language Java. Although, Java was my first programming language, I have great interest learning more programming languages. I wish to gain more knowledge about both front-end and back-end web development work. I believe that working with your organization and learning on the job will be decisive step forward in my programming career.

Work Experience

Front End Web Developer and Designer

430 Designs

December 2017 to Present

430 Designs

- Worked on websites using WordPress.
- Manipulated the DOM using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and JQuery.
- Worked with a team to accomplish tasks using the sprint method.
- Used the Version Control System .Git to push and pull from each projects repository.
- Worked with the FTP Client (FileZilla) to pull directories from the server to clone the parent site and create a child/development site to work on.

Web Designer/Developer

STEED International

August 2016 to August 2017

- Designed the Landing Page with Photoshop Elements.
- Developed the website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript Plugins.

Education

Associate and Bachelors in Cyber and Network Security AS $\!\!/$ Software Development BS

ECPI University
November 2018 to November 2020

Associate in General Studies

Northern Virginia Community College 2014 to 2016

Skills

HTML5, CSS, Vanilla JavaScript, Node.js, React.js, JQuery, Windows Command Line, Java, C, PHP, MySQL, SASS, Photoshop, Python, .Git, UI, C++, Adobe Premier

Additional Information

Portfolio:

https://github.com/Conan-Official/Work-Portfolio.git